export const striverSheetData = {
  Arrays: [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_1",
      problem: "Set Matrix Zeroes",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/set-matrix-zeroes/",

      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N0MgLvceX7M&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=28",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/set-matrix-zeros_3846774?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_2",
      problem: "Pascal's Triangle",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/pascals-triangle/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bR7mQgwQ_o8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=32",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rhv153",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_3",
      problem: "Next Permutation",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/next-permutation/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JDOXKqF60RQ&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=25",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qoj5iQ",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_4",
      problem: "Kadane's Algorithm",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-subarray/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AHZpyENo7k4&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=22",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3HZltTa",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_5",
      problem: "Sort an array of 0’s 1’s 2’s",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sort-colors/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tp8JIuCXBaU&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=20",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tlM60B",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_6",
      problem: "Stock buy and Sell",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=excAOvwF_Wk&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=23",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GsANaD",
    },
  ],
  "Arrays Part-II": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_7",
      problem: "Rotate Matrix",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/rotate-image/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z0R2u6gd3GU&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=29",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rhVUWx",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_8",
      problem: "Merge Overlapping Subintervals",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-intervals/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IexN60k62jo&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=37",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rj9LvO",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_9",
      problem: "Merge two sorted Arrays without extra space",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-sorted-array/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n7uwj04E0I4&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=38",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33umm7e",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_10",
      problem: "Find the duplicate in an array of N+1 integers",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-duplicate-number/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=32Ll35mhWg0&list=PLgUwDviBIf0rPG3Ictpu74YWBQ1CaBkm2&index=1",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GtKDJb",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_11",
      problem: "Repeat and Missing Number",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/repeat-and-missing-number-array/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/2D0D8HE6uak",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gs6wZu",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_12",
      problem: "Inversion of Array (Pre-req: Merge Sort)",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/count-inversions_615",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AseUmwVNaoY&ab_channel=takeUforward",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/339fFb7",
    },
  ],
  "Arrays Part-III": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_13",
      problem: "Search in a 2d Matrix",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-a-2d-matrix/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZYpYur0znng&list=PLgUwDviBIf0rPG3Ictpu74YWBQ1CaBkm2&index=14",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GD7NNa",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_14",
      problem: "Pow(X,n)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/powx-n/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l0YC3876qxg&list=PLgUwDviBIf0rPG3Ictpu74YWBQ1CaBkm2&index=15",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gtjwhl",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_15",
      problem: "Majority Element (>N/2 times)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/majority-element/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nP_ns3uSh80&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=21",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FpfpBQ",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_16",
      problem: "Majority Element (>N/3 times)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/majority-element-ii/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vwZj1K0e9U8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=33",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3foYLYp",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_17",
      problem: "Grid Unique Paths",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/unique-paths/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/t_f0nwwdg5o",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fm1dyN",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_18",
      problem: "Reverse Pairs (Leetcode)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-pairs/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/0e4bZaP3MDI",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tm5PgF",
    },
  ],
  "Arrays Part-IV": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_19",
      problem: "2-Sum-Problem",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UXDSeD9mN-k&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=19",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3riXBmz",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_20",
      problem: "4-sum-Problem",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/4sum/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eD95WRfh81c&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=35",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qpfEsj",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_21",
      problem: "Longest Consecutive Sequence",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-consecutive-sequence/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oO5uLE7EUlM&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=28",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/34EoAS0",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_22",
      problem: "Largest Subarray with K sum",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/largest-subarray-with-0-sum/1",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/frf7qxiN2qU",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31UHoeM",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_23",
      problem: "Count number of subarrays with given Xor K",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/subarray-with-given-xor/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eZr-6p0B7ME&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oF6QL8m22w1hIDC1vJ_BHz&index=36",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fp24yN",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_24",
      problem: "Longest Substring without repeat",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-substring-without-repeating-characters/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qtVh-XEpsJo&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=26",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3no44fb",
    },
  ],
  "Linked List": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_25",
      problem: "Reverse a LinkedList",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-linked-list/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iRtLEoL-r-g&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=27",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qoE6K6",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_26",
      problem: "Find the middle of LinkedList",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/middle-of-the-linked-list/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sGdwSH8RK-o&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=28",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KcRxoG",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_27",
      problem: "Merge two sorted Linked List (use method used in mergeSort)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-two-sorted-lists/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xb4slcp1U38&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=29",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qnbSj8",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_28",
      problem: "Remove N-th node from back of LinkedList",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-nth-node-from-end-of-list/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lhu3MsXZy-Q&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=30",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3riZ4JB",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_29",
      problem: "Add two numbers as LinkedList",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/add-two-numbers/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LBVsXSMOIk4&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=32",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qqbgcq",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_30",
      problem: "Delete a given Node when a node is given.(0(1) solution)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/delete-node-in-a-linked-list/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=icnp4FJdZ_c&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=31",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GqW4kN",
    },
  ],
  "Linked List Part-II": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_31",
      problem: "Find intersection point of Y LinkedList",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/intersection-of-two-linked-lists/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u4FWXfgS8jw&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=33",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fiMQeG",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_32",
      problem: "Detect a cycle in Linked List",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/linked-list-cycle/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=354J83hX7RI&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=34",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I2fmxh",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_33",
      problem: "Reverse a LinkedList in groups of size k.",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-nodes-in-k-group/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Of0HPkk3JgI&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=34",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gsfk1u",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_34",
      problem: "Check if a LinkedList is palindrome or not.",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/palindrome-linked-list/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-DtNInqFUXs&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=36",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GqRMKv",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_35",
      problem: "Find the starting point of the Loop of LinkedList",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/linked-list-cycle-ii/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QfbOhn0WZ88&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=37",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K32lpf",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_36",
      problem: "Flattening of a LinkedList",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/flattening-a-linked-list/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ysytSSXpAI0&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=38",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nqtEA1",
    },
  ],
  "Linked List and Arrays": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_37",
      problem: "Rotate a LinkedList",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/rotate-list/description/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9VPm6nEbVPA&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=39",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33bNQPo",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_38",
      problem: "Clone a Linked List with random and next pointer",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/copy-list-with-random-pointer/",
      videoSolution: "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VNf6VynfpdM",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qnFoFg",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_39",
      problem: "3 sum",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/3sum/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=onLoX6Nhvmg&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=41",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33wlWxk",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_40",
      problem: "Trapping rainwater",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/trapping-rain-water/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m18Hntz4go8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=42",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KcxExJ",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_41",
      problem: "Remove Duplicate from Sorted array",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-duplicates-from-sorted-array/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fm_p9lJ4Z_8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=43",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31Usllh",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_42",
      problem: "Max consecutive ones",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/max-consecutive-ones/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mo33MjjMlyA&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=44",
      codingNinja: "https://leetcode.com/problems/max-consecutive-ones/",
    },
  ],
  "Greedy Algorithm": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_43",
      problem: "N meetings in one room",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/n-meetings-in-one-room-1587115620/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=II6ziNnub1Q&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=45",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zXdqn5",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_44",
      problem: "Minimum number of platforms required for a railway",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/minimum-platforms-1587115620/1#",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dxVcMDI7vyI&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=46",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3npx0mW",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_45",
      problem: "Job sequencing Problem",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/job-sequencing-problem-1587115620/1#",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LjPx4wQaRIs&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=47",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K9XZfV",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_46",
      problem: "Fractional Knapsack Problem",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/fractional-knapsack-1587115620/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_DDzYnxO14&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=49",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I7fNXn",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_47",
      problem: "Greedy algorithm to find minimum number of coins",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.geeksforgeeks.org/find-minimum-number-of-coins-that-make-a-change/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mVg9CfJvayM&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=48",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nquVHj",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_48",
      problem: "Activity Selection (it is the same as N meeting in one room)",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/n-meetings-in-one-room-1587115620/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=II6ziNnub1Q&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=45",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I2iPvN",
    },
  ],
  "Recursion ": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_49",
      problem: "Subset Sums",
      leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/subset-sums2234/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rYkfBRtMJr8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=52",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/subset-sum_3843086?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_50",
      problem: "Subset-II",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/subsets-ii/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RIn3gOkbhQE&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=53",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qnaLjq",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_51",
      problem: "Combination sum-1",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OyZFFqQtu98&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=49",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qpmDS1",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_52",
      problem: "Combination sum-2",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum-ii/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G1fRTGRxXU8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=50",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tkbtjk",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_53",
      problem: "Palindrome Partitioning",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/palindrome-partitioning/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WBgsABoClE0&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=51",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3HZPNgs",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_54",
      problem: "K-th permutation Sequence",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/permutation-sequence/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wT7gcXLYoao&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=55",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KcCP0D",
    },
  ],
  "Recursion and Backtracking": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_55",
      problem: "Print all permutations of a string/array",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/permutations/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f2ic2Rsc9pU&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=52",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fmwxNV",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_56",
      problem: "N queens Problem",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/n-queens/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i05Ju7AftcM&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=57",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zSZavC",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_57",
      problem: "Sudoku Solver",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sudoku-solver/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FWAIf_EVUKE&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=58",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31Z5Iwe",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_58",
      problem: "M coloring Problem",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/m-coloring-problem-1587115620/1#",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wuVwUK25Rfc&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=59",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I48oI6",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_59",
      problem: "Rat in a Maze",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/rat-in-a-maze-problem/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bLGZhJlt4y0&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=60",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fmwP7t",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_60",
      problem: "Word Break (print all ways)",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FxgW92",
    },
  ],
  "Binary Search": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_61",
      problem: "The N-th root of an integer",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WjpswYrS2nY&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=62",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rj7Ib1",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_62",
      problem: "Matrix Median",
      leetCode: "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/matrix-median/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=63fPPOdIr2c&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=62",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33AHZTz",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_63",
      problem:
        "Find the element that appears once in a sorted array, and the rest element appears twice (Binary search)",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/single-element-in-a-sorted-array/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PzszoiY5XMQ&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=64",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rng2qC",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_64",
      problem:
        "Search element in a sorted and rotated array/ find pivot where it is rotated",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-rotated-sorted-array/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r3pMQ8-Ad5s&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=64",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nnxGcm",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_65",
      problem: "Median of 2 sorted arrays",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/median-of-two-sorted-arrays/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NTop3VTjmxk&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=65",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Ka3jQr",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_66",
      problem: "K-th element of two sorted arrays",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/k-th-element-of-two-sorted-array1317/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nv7F4PiLUzo&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=66",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qm0cgu",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_67",
      problem: "Allocate Minimum Number of Pages",
      leetCode: "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/allocate-books/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gYmWHvRHu-s&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=69",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FrKxk7",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_68",
      problem: "Aggressive Cows",
      leetCode: "https://www.spoj.com/problems/AGGRCOW/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wSOfYesTBRk&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=70",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zV52ob",
    },
  ],
  Heaps: [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_69",
      problem: "Max heap, Min Heap Implementation (Only for interviews)",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/min-heap_4691801?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_70",
      problem: "Kth Largest Element",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-an-array/",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/kth-smallest-and-largest-element-of-array_1115488?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_71",
      problem: "Maximum Sum Combination",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/maximum-sum-combinations/",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/k-max-sum-combinations_975322?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_72",
      problem: "Find Median from Data Stream",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-median-from-data-stream/",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/running-median_625409?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_73",
      problem: "Merge K sorted arrays",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/merge-k-sorted-arrays_975379",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/merge-k-sorted-arrays_975379?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_74",
      problem: "K most frequent elements",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/top-k-frequent-elements/",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/k-most-frequent-elements_3167808?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    },
  ],
  "Stack and Queue": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_75",
      problem: "Implement Stack Using Arrays",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GYptUgnIM_I&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=68",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/stack-implementation-using-array_3210209",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_76",
      problem: "Implement Queue Using Arrays",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M6GnoUDpqEE&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=72",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KbIjIW",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_77",
      problem: "Implement Stack using Queue (using single queue)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-stack-using-queues/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jDZQKzEtbYQ&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=74",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3reLgQs",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_78",
      problem: "Implement Queue using Stack (0(1) amortized method)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-queue-using-stacks/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Et9MrMc02A&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=75",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3reLeIk",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_79",
      problem: "Check for balanced parentheses",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-parentheses/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wkDfsKijrZ8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=74",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nr1RiO",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_80",
      problem: "Next Greater Element",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/next-greater-element-ii/description/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Du881K7Jtk8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=75",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qyCjCF",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_81",
      problem: "Sort a Stack",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nptF7k",
    },
  ],
  "Stack and Queue Part-II": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_82",
      problem: "Next Smaller Element",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/nearest-smaller-element/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K6WVtb",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_83",
      problem: "LRU cache (IMPORTANT)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/lru-cache/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xDEuM5qa0zg&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=77",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K7Cs7I",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_84",
      problem: "LFU Cache",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/lfu-cache/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0PSB9y8ehbk&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=79",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3noxuK0",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_85",
      problem: "Largest rectangle in a histogram",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/largest-rectangle-in-histogram/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X0X6G-eWgQ8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=81",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qpxbR9",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_86",
      problem: "Sliding Window maximum",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sliding-window-maximum/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CZQGRp93K4k&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=83",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GmTkoC",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_87",
      problem: "Implement Min Stack",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/min-stack/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/V09NfaGf2ao",
      codingNinja:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/min-stack_3843991?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_88",
      problem: "Rotten Orange (Using BFS)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/rotting-oranges/",
      videoSolution: "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yf3oUhkvqA0",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33zH0TC",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_89",
      problem: "Stock Span Problem",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/online-stock-span/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GvBtMk",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_90",
      problem: "Find the maximum of minimums of every window size",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zUYLZz",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_91",
      problem: "The Celebrity Problem",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/accounts/login/?next=/problems/find-the-celebrity/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GuImxi",
    },
  ],
  String: [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_92",
      problem: "Reverse Words in a String",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-words-in-a-string/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FmKc1X",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_93",
      problem: "Longest Palindrome in a string",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-palindromic-substring/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Grdrlv",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_94",
      problem: "Roman Number to Integer and vice versa",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/roman-to-integer/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rkGuBb",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_95",
      problem: "Implement ATOI/STRSTR",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/string-to-integer-atoi/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zXpYeb",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_96",
      problem: "Longest Common Prefix",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-common-prefix/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GlNN1D",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_97",
      problem: "Rabin Karp",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/repeated-string-match/discuss/416144/Rabin-Karp-algorithm-C%2B%2B-implementation",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FvnLaN",
    },
  ],
  "String Part-II": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_98",
      problem: "Z-Function",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-strstr/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qs24UM",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_99",
      problem: "KMP algo / LPS(pi) array",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-strstr/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31VF1s6",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_100",
      problem:
        "Minimum characters needed to be inserted in the beginning to make it palindromic",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/minimum-characters-required-to-make-a-string-palindromic/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/34RE855",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_101",
      problem: "Check for Anagrams",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-anagram/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K6weoJ",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_102",
      problem: "Count and Say",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-and-say/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K8Uwyi",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_103",
      problem: "Compare version numbers",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/compare-version-numbers/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GwYuys",
    },
  ],
  "Binary Tree": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_104",
      problem: "Inorder Traversal",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-inorder-traversal/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z_NEgBgbRVI&list=PLgUwDviBIf0q8Hkd7bK2Bpryj2xVJk8Vk&index=7",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_105",
      problem: "Preorder Traversal",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-preorder-traversal/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/RlUu72JrOCQ",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_106",
      problem: "Postorder Traversal",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-postorder-traversal/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/COQOU6klsBg",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_107",
      problem: "Morris Inorder Traversal",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-inorder-traversal/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=80Zug6D1_r4&list=PLgUwDviBIf0q8Hkd7bK2Bpryj2xVJk8Vk&index=38",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_108",
      problem: "Morris Preorder Traversal",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/80Zug6D1_r4",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_109",
      problem: "LeftView Of Binary Tree",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/left-view-of-binary-tree/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KV4mRzTjlAk&list=PLgUwDviBIf0q8Hkd7bK2Bpryj2xVJk8Vk&index=25",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GtxyQa",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_110",
      problem: "Bottom View of Binary Tree",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/bottom-view-of-binary-tree/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0FtVY6I4pB8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0q8Hkd7bK2Bpryj2xVJk8Vk&index=24",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3trqFLq",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_111",
      problem: "Top View of Binary Tree",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/top-view-of-binary-tree/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Et9OCDNvJ78&list=PLgUwDviBIf0q8Hkd7bK2Bpryj2xVJk8Vk&index=23",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gs76WV",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_112",
      problem: "Preorder inorder postorder in a single traversal",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/ySp2epYvgTE",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rlXpTX",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_113",
      problem: "Vertical order traversal",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/vertical-order-traversal-of-a-binary-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/q_a6lpbKJdw",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KaM41v",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_114",
      problem: "Root to node path in a Binary Tree",
      leetCode: "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/path-to-given-node/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/fmflMqVOC7k",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_115",
      problem: "Max width of a Binary Tree",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-width-of-binary-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/ZbybYvcVLks",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rm014d",
    },
  ],
  "Binary Tree part-II": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_116",
      problem: "Level order Traversal / Level order traversal in spiral form",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-level-order-traversal/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/EoAsWbO7sqg",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zVtSnX",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_117",
      problem: "Height of a Binary Tree",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-depth-of-binary-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/eD3tmO66aBA",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qoOEco",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_118",
      problem: "Diameter of Binary Tree",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/diameter-of-binary-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/Rezetez59Nk",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I3O1uD",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_119",
      problem: "Check if the Binary tree is height-balanced or not",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/balanced-binary-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/Yt50Jfbd8Po",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fqsvnA",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_120",
      problem: "LCA in Binary Tree",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/_-QHfMDde90",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tqcRko",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_121",
      problem: "Check if two trees are identical or not",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/same-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/BhuvF_-PWS0",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GuQYnE",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_122",
      problem: "Zig Zag Traversal of Binary Tree",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-zigzag-level-order-traversal/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/3OXWEdlIGl4",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GrS3g7",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_123",
      problem: "Boundary Traversal of Binary Tree",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/boundary-of-binary-tree/#",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/0ca1nvR0be4",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GxQ6yH",
    },
  ],
  "Binary Tree part-III": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_124",
      problem: "Maximum path sum",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-maximum-path-sum/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/WszrfSwMz58",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rkQUR4",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_125",
      problem: "Construct Binary Tree from inorder and preorder",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/aZNaLrVebKQ",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fqOif3",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_126",
      problem: "Construct Binary Tree from Inorder and Postorder",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-tree-from-inorder-and-postorder-traversal/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/LgLRTaEMRVc",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qrzumM",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_127",
      problem: "Symmetric Binary Tree",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/symmetric-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/nKggNAiEpBE",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GItN9P",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_128",
      problem: "Flatten Binary Tree to LinkedList",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/flatten-binary-tree-to-linked-list/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/sWf7k1x9XR4",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qA9uWt",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_129",
      problem: "Check if Binary Tree is the mirror of itself or not",
      leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/mirror-tree/1",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nqSnnQ",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_130",
      problem: "Check for Children Sum Property",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/fnmisPM6cVo",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33yExIQ",
    },
  ],
  "Binary Search Tree": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_131",
      problem: "Populate Next Right pointers of Tree",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/populating-next-right-pointers-in-each-node/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33Bm8uX",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_132",
      problem: "Search given Key in BST",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-a-binary-search-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/KcNt6v_56cc",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Ft26jR",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_133",
      problem: "Construct BST from given keys",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/convert-sorted-array-to-binary-search-tree/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qr5I1t",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_134",
      problem: "Construct BST from preorder traversal",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-search-tree-from-preorder-traversal/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/UmJT3j26t1I",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Fr7GTQ",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_135",
      problem: "Check is a BT is BST or not",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/validate-binary-search-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/f-sj7I5oXEI",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nmKek7",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_136",
      problem: "Find LCA of two nodes in BST",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-search-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/cX_kPV_foZc",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qqoaXM",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_137",
      problem: "Find the inorder predecessor/successor of a given Key in BST.",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/predecessor-and-successor/1",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/SXKAD2svfmI",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3A0hm6l",
    },
  ],
  "Binary Search Tree Part-II": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_138",
      problem: "Floor in a BST",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/floor-from-bst_920457?source=youtube&campaign=Striver_Tree_Videos&utm_source=youtube&utm_medium=affiliate&utm_campaign=Striver_Tree_Videos",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xm_W1ub-K-w&list=PLgUwDviBIf0q8Hkd7bK2Bpryj2xVJk8Vk&index=43",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nsqdbY",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_139",
      problem: "Ceil in a BST",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/ceil-from-bst_920464?source=youtube&campaign=Striver_Tree_Videos&utm_source=youtube&utm_medium=affiliate&utm_campaign=Striver_Tree_Videos",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KSsk8AhdOZA&list=PLgUwDviBIf0q8Hkd7bK2Bpryj2xVJk8Vk&index=42",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33b9enW",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_140",
      problem: "Find K-th smallest element in BST",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-smallest-element-in-a-bst/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/9TJYWh0adfk",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rf0HrP",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_141",
      problem: "Find K-th largest element in BST",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/kth-largest-element-in-bst/1",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/9TJYWh0adfk",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31Yjtet",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_142",
      problem: "Find a pair with a given sum in BST",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum-iv-input-is-a-bst/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/ssL3sHwPeb4",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FvDAOO",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_143",
      problem: "BST iterator",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-search-tree-iterator/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/D2jMcmxU4bs",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FsH5FC",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_144",
      problem: "Size of the largest BST in a Binary Tree",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-sum-bst-in-binary-tree/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/X0oXMdtUDwo",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fn6h5V",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_145",
      problem: "Serialize and deserialize Binary Tree",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/serialize-and-deserialize-binary-tree/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-YbXySKJsX8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0q8Hkd7bK2Bpryj2xVJk8Vk&index=37",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qr6pYD",
    },
  ],
  "Binary Trees[Miscellaneous]": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_146",
      problem: "Binary Tree to Double Linked List",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/flatten-binary-tree-to-linked-list/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sWf7k1x9XR4&list=PLgUwDviBIf0q8Hkd7bK2Bpryj2xVJk8Vk&index=39",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3HVnGz0",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_147",
      problem: "Find median in a stream of running integers.",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-median-from-data-stream/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rkTB58",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_148",
      problem: "K-th largest element in a stream.",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-a-stream/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KdiUPp",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_149",
      problem: "Distinct numbers in Window.",
      leetCode:
        "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/distinct-numbers-in-window/",
      codingNinja:
        "https://takeuforward.org/interviews/strivers-sde-sheet-top-coding-interview-problems/bit.ly/3zYWpcb",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_150",
      problem: "K-th largest element in an unsorted array.",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-an-array/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GvQttz",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_151",
      problem: "Flood-fill Algorithm",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/flood-fill/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gv1Th5",
    },
  ],
  Graph: [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_152",
      problem: "Clone a graph (Not that easy as it looks)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/clone-graph/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33BcVmE",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_153",
      problem: "DFS",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/depth-first-traversal-for-a-graph/1",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/Qzf1a--rhp8",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33BcXeg",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_154",
      problem: "BFS",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/bfs-traversal-of-graph/1",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/-tgVpUgsQ5k",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rgb26U",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_155",
      problem: "Detect A cycle in Undirected Graph using BFS",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/BPlrALf1LDU",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3npFdrn",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_156",
      problem: "Detect A cycle in Undirected Graph using DFS",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/zQ3zgFypzX4",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3npFdrn",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_157",
      problem: "Detect A cycle in a Directed Graph using DFS",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uzVUw90ZFIg&list=PLgUwDviBIf0rGEWe64KWas0Nryn7SCRWw&index=12",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FrzaZp",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_158",
      problem: "Detect A cycle in a Directed Graph using BFS",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iTBaI90lpDQ&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=23",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FrzaZp",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_159",
      problem: "Topological Sort BFS",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/topological-sort/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=73sneFXuTEg&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=22",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33bapUo",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_160",
      problem: "Topological Sort DFS",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/topological-sort/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5lZ0iJMrUMk&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=22",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33bapUo",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_161",
      problem: "Number of islands(Do in Grid and Graph Both)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-islands/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=muncqlKJrH0&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=8",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KaSCND",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_162",
      problem: "Bipartite Check using BFS",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/is-graph-bipartite/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-vu34sct1g8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=17",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tps98W",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_163",
      problem: "Bipartite Check using DFS",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/is-graph-bipartite/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KG5YFfR0j8A&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=18",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tps98W",
    },
  ],
  "Graph Part-II": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_164",
      problem: "Strongly Connected Component(using KosaRaju’s algo)",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-number-of-non-overlapping-substrings/discuss/766485/kosaraju-algorithm-on",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V8qIqJxCioo&list=PLgUwDviBIf0rGEWe64KWas0Nryn7SCRWw&index=27",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3twUKJP",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_165",
      problem: "Dijkstra’s Algorithm",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/implementing-dijkstra-set-1-adjacency-matrix/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rp1SMw7HSO8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=35",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qrEHLm",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_166",
      problem: "Bellman-Ford Algo",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/distance-from-the-source-bellman-ford-algorithm/0/?fbclid=IwAR2_lL0T84DnciLyzMTQuVTMBOi82nTWNLuXjUgahnrtBgkphKiYk6xcyJU",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0vVofAhAYjc&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=41",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GwAf3A",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_167",
      problem: "Floyd Warshall Algorithm",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/implementing-floyd-warshall2042/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YbY8cVwWAvw&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=42",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Kb41Ny",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_168",
      problem: "MST using Prim’s Algo",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/minimum-spanning-tree/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mJcZjjKzeqk&list=PLgUwDviBIf0oE3gA41TKO2H5bHpPd7fzn&index=44",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I5Ktbi",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_169",
      problem: "MST using Kruskal’s Algo",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/minimum-spanning-tree/1",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1KRmCzBl_mQ&list=PLgUwDviBIf0rGEWe64KWas0Nryn7SCRWw&index=24",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I1VqL9",
    },
  ],
  "Dynamic Programming": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_170",
      problem: "Max Product Subarray",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-product-subarray/",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fqz6OS",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_171",
      problem: "Longest Increasing Subsequence",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-increasing-subsequence/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/ekcwMsSIzVc",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GuWGpA",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_172",
      problem: "Longest Common Subsequence",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-common-subsequence/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/NPZn9jBrX8U",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3raZbqM",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_173",
      problem: "0-1 Knapsack",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/0-1-knapsack-problem0945/1",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/GqOmJHQZivw",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FvHbMO",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_174",
      problem: "Edit Distance",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/edit-distance/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/fJaKO8FbDdo",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qpUHgE",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_175",
      problem: "Maximum sum increasing subsequence",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/maximum-sum-increasing-subsequence4749/1",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tqiS0s",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_176",
      problem: "Matrix Chain Multiplication",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/matrix-chain-multiplication0303/1",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/vRVfmbCFW7Y",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qqX56T",
    },
  ],
  "Dynamic Programming Part-II": [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_177",
      problem:
        "Minimum sum path in the matrix, (count paths and similar type do, also backtrack to find the Minimum path)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-path-sum/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/_rgTlyky1uQ",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zWJEin",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_178",
      problem: "Coin change",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/coin-change/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/HgyouUi11zk",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GwBrnA",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_179",
      problem: "Subset Sum",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/partition-equal-subset-sum/",
      videoSolution: "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fWX9xDmIzRI",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rjUdb7",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_180",
      problem: "Rod Cutting",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-cost-to-cut-a-stick/",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/mO8XpGoJwuo",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GuIsoS",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_181",
      problem: "Egg Dropping",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/egg-dropping-puzzle-1587115620/1",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3A6id5O",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_182",
      problem: "Word Break",
      leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/word-break1352/1",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3npqs7P",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_183",
      problem: "Palindrome Partitioning (MCM Variation)",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/palindromic-patitioning4845/1",
      videoSolution: "https://youtu.be/_H8V5hJUGd0",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tq9MRn",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_184",
      problem: "Maximum profit in Job scheduling",
      leetCode:
        "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/job-sequencing-problem-1587115620/1",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/34FoY2C",
    },
  ],
  Trie: [
    {
      checkbox: "ques_185",
      problem: "Implement Trie (Prefix Tree)",
      leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-trie-prefix-tree/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dBGUmUQhjaM&list=PLgUwDviBIf0pcIDCZnxhv0LkHf5KzG9zp",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33wIn5x",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_186",
      problem: "Implement Trie – 2 (Prefix Tree)",
      leetCode: "https://bit.ly/3qwT4OL",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K5pcpkEMCN0&list=PLgUwDviBIf0pcIDCZnxhv0LkHf5KzG9zp&index=2",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I8Q9l7",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_187",
      problem: "Longest String with All Prefixes",
      leetCode: "https://bit.ly/3n3kedU",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AWnBa91lThI&list=PLgUwDviBIf0pcIDCZnxhv0LkHf5KzG9zp&index=3",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qrU6vb",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_188",
      problem: "Number of Distinct Substrings in a String",
      leetCode: "https://bit.ly/3ocRQW0",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RV0QeTyHZxo&list=PLgUwDviBIf0pcIDCZnxhv0LkHf5KzG9zp&index=4",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zVV1XD",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_189",
      problem: "Power Set (this is very important)",
      leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/power-set4302/1#",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b7AYbpM5YrE&list=PLgUwDviBIf0p4ozDR_kJJkONnb1wdx2Ma&index=67",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fmd28k",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_190",
      problem: "Maximum XOR of two numbers in an array",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-xor-of-two-numbers-in-an-array/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EIhAwfHubE8&list=PLgUwDviBIf0pcIDCZnxhv0LkHf5KzG9zp&index=6",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rjEYis",
    },
    {
      checkbox: "ques_191",
      problem: "Maximum XOR With an Element From Array",
      leetCode:
        "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-xor-with-an-element-from-array/",
      videoSolution:
        "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q8LhG9Pi5KM&list=PLgUwDviBIf0pcIDCZnxhv0LkHf5KzG9zp&index=7",
      codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KbHhN4",
    },
  ],
} as {
  [key: string]: {
    checkbox: string;
    problem: string;
    leetCode: string;
    videoSolution?: string;
    codingNinja: string;
  }[];
};
type SSRelation = Record<string, number>[];
export const ssRelation: SSRelation = [
  {
    Arrays: 1,
  },
  {
    "Arrays Part-II": 2,
  },
  {
    "Arrays Part-III": 3,
  },
  {
    "Arrays Part-IV": 4,
  },
  {
    "Linked List": 5,
  },
  {
    "Linked List Part-II": 6,
  },
  {
    "Linked List and Arrays": 7,
  },
  {
    "Greedy Algorithm": 8,
  },
  {
    "Recursion ": 9,
  },
  {
    "Recursion and Backtracking": 10,
  },
  {
    "Binary Search": 11,
  },
  {
    Heaps: 12,
  },
  {
    "Stack and Queue": 13,
  },
  {
    "Stack and Queue Part-II": 14,
  },
  {
    String: 15,
  },
  {
    "String Part-II": 16,
  },
  {
    "Binary Tree": 17,
  },
  {
    "Binary Tree part-II": 18,
  },
  {
    "Binary Tree part-III": 19,
  },
  {
    "Binary Search Tree": 20,
  },
  {
    "Binary Search Tree Part-II": 21,
  },
  {
    "Binary Trees[Miscellaneous]": 22,
  },
  {
    Graph: 23,
  },
  {
    "Graph Part-II": 24,
  },
  {
    "Dynamic Programming": 25,
  },
  {
    "Dynamic Programming Part-II": 26,
  },
  {
    Trie: 27,
  },
];
